<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Connect</string>
    <string name="nav_open">Open</string>
    <string name="nav_close">Close</string>
    <string name="safe">"Your area is safe."</string>
    <string name="warning">"Warning!\n\nBe prepared for the upcoming disaster!"</string>
    <string name="danger">"Danger!\n\nMove to a safe place and stay connected."</string>
    <string name="complete_profile">"Please update your profile!"</string>
    <string name="beforeflood"><b><p>To prepare for a flood, you should:</p></b>
        \n\n
<ul>


<li>Avoid building in a floodplain unless you elevate and reinforce your home.\n\n</li>
<li>Elevate the furnace, water heater and electric panel in your home if you live in an area that has a high flood risk.\n\n</li>
<li>Consider installing "check valves" to prevent flood water from backing up into the drains of your home.\n\n</li>
<li>If feasible, construct barriers to stop floodwater from entering the building and seal walls in basements with waterproofing compounds.\n\n</li>
</ul>
    </string>

    <string name="duringflood"><b><p>If a flood is likely in your area, you should:</p></b>\n\n
<ul>
<li>Listen to the radio or television for information.\n\n</li>
<li>Be aware that flash flooding can occur. If there is any possibility of a flash flood, move immediately to higher ground. Do not wait for instructions to move.\n\n</li>
<li>Be aware of stream, drainage channels, canyons and other areas known to flood suddenly. Flash floods can occur in these areas with or without typical warnings such as rain clouds or heavy rain.\n\n</li>
</ul><p><b>If you must prepare to evacuate, you should do the following:</b>\n\n</p>
<ul>
<li>Secure your home. If you have time, bring in outdoor furniture. Move essential items to an upper floor.\n\n</li>
<li>Turn off the main switches or valves if instructed to do so.\n\n</li>
<li>Disconnect electrical appliances.\n\n</li>
<li>Do not touch electrical equipment if you are wet or standing in water.\n\n</li>
</ul>
    </string>

    <string name="afterflood"><b><p>Although floodwaters may be down in some areas, many dangers still exist. Here are some things to remember in the days ahead:</p></b>\n\n
<ul>
<li>Avoid moving water.\n\n</li>
<li>Stay away from damaged areas unless your assistance has been specifically requested by police, fire, or relief organization.\n\n</li>
<li>Emergency workers will be assisting people in flooded areas. You can help them by staying off the roads and out of the way.\n\n</li>
<li>Return home only when authorities indicate it is safe.\n\n</li>

</ul><b><p>Staying Healthy</p></b>\n\n
<p>A flood can cause physical hazards and emotional stress. You need to look after yourself and your family as you focus on cleanup and repair.</p>\n\n
<ul>
<li>Avoid floodwaters; water may be contaminated by oil, gasoline or raw sewage.\n\n</li>
<li>Clean and disinfect everything that got wet. Mud left from floodwaters can contain sewage and chemicals.\n\n</li>
<li>Rest often and eat well.\n\n</li>
<li>Discuss your concerns with others and seek help. Contact Red Cross for information on emotional support available in your area.\n\n</li>
</ul>
<b>Cleaning up And Repairing Your Home</b>\n\n
<ul>
<li>Turn off the electricity at the main breaker or fuse box, even if the power is off in your community. That way, you can decide when your home is dry enough to turn it back on.\n\n</li>
<li>Enter your home safely.\n\n</li>
<li>Protect your home and belongings from further damage.\n\n</li>
<li>Record damage to support insurance claims and requests for assistance.\n\n</li>
<li>Check for gas or water leaks and how to have service restored.\n\n</li>
<li>Clean up appliances, furniture, floors and other belongs.\n\n</li>
<li>Contact your insurance agent to discuss claims.\n\n</li>
<li>Listen to your radio for information on assistance that may be provided by the state or federal government or other organizations.\n\n</li>
<li>If you hire cleanup or repair contractors, check references and be sure they are qualified to do the job. Be wary of people who drive through neighborhoods offering help in cleaning up or repairing your home.\n\n</li>
</ul>


</string>
    <string name="beforeearthquake"><b>What to Do Before an Earthquake\n\n</b>
<ul>
<li>Make sure you have a fire extinguisher, first aid kit, a battery-powered radio, a flashlight, and extra batteries at home.\n\n</li>
<li>Learn first aid.\n\n</li>
<li>Learn how to turn off the gas, water, and electricity.\n</li>
<li>Make up a plan of where to meet your family after an earthquake.\n\n</li>
<li>Do not leave heavy objects on shelves (they will fall during a quake).\n\n</li>
<li>Anchor heavy furniture, cupboards, and appliances to the walls or floor.\n\n</li>
<li>Learn the earthquake plan at your school or workplace.\n</li>
</ul>

    </string>

    <string name="duringearthquake"><b>What to Do During an Earthquake\n\n</b>
<ul>
<li><b>Stay calm.</b> If you are indoors, stay inside. If you are outside, stay outside.\n\n</li>
 <li>If you are indoors, stand against a wall near the center of the building.\n\n</li>
<li>stand in a doorway, or crawl under heavy furniture.a desk or table. Stay away from windows and outside doors.\n\n</li>
<li>If you are outdoors, stay in the open away from power lines or anything that might fall. Stay away from buildings.\n\n </li>
<li>Do not use matches, candles, or any flame. Broken gas lines and fire do not mix.\n\n</li>
<li>If you are in a car, stop the car and stay inside the car until the earthquake stops.\n\n</li>
 <li>Do not use elevators .they may shut down.\n</li>
</ul>

    </string>
    <string name="afterearthquake"><b>What to Do After an Earthquake\n\n</b>
<ul>
<li>Check yourself and others for injuries. Provide first aid for anyone who needs it.\n\n</li>
<li>Check water, gas, and electric lines for damage.\n\n </li>

<li>Turn on the radio. Do not use the phone unless it is an emergency.\n\n</li>
<li>Stay out of damaged buildings.\n\n</li>
<li>Be careful around broken glass and debris. Wear boots or sturdy shoes to keep from cutting your feet.\n\n</li>
<li>Be careful of chimneys .they may fall on you.\n\n</li>
<li>Stay away from beaches. Tsunamis sometimes hit after the ground has stopped shaking.\n\n</li>
<li>Stay away from damaged areas.\n\n</li>
<li>If you are at school or work, follow the emergency plan or the instructions of the person in charge.\n\n</li>
</ul>

    </string>
    <string name="beforecyclone"><b>Precautions of cyclone \n\n</b>
<ul>
<li>Ensure good condition of your house so that it can withstand strong winds.\n\n</li>
<li>Trim down trees to make sure they do not fall over telephone or electricity lines during the storm.\n\n</li>
<li>Keep your mobile phone fully charged and other appliances like torches handy as there may be power cuts during a cyclone.\n\n</li>
<li>Store essential items like groceries and medicines in advance. It is vital to keep dry foods that are not perishable during emergencies.\n\n</li>
<li>Prepare an emergency first-aid kit.\n\n</li>
<li>Store water because the water supply may be disrupted during cyclones.\n\n</li>
</ul>
        <p><b>Apart from the above cyclone precautions, one should avoid some factors at any cost while preparing for a storm. They are as follows:\n\n</b></p>
<ul>
<li>Do not leave any loose sharp objects lying around your property, as they can injure people during gusty winds.\n\n</li>
<li>It is vital to steer clear of demolished buildings during cyclones.\n\n</li>
<li>Do not keep dying and low-hanging branches of trees near your premises.\n\n</li>
</ul>

    </string>
    <string name="duringcyclone"><b>Safety measures to be taken during a cyclone \n\n</b>
<ul>
<li>Be aware of the official cyclone warning by listening to the radio or other authentic sources.\n\n</li>
<li>Install storm shutters or board up glass windows.\n\n</li>
<li>Keep all the doors and windows closed.\n\n</li>
<li>Take proper care of adults or children who need attention.\n\n</li>
<li>Switch off the electrical mains in your house.\n\n</li>
<li>Park your vehicles beneath a solid shelter with a hand brake or in gear to guard them.\n\n</li>
</ul>
        <p><b>Other than this, if the eye of the cyclone passes over your house, you should strictly avoid doing some activities as follows:\n\n </b></p>
<ul>
<li>If you are asked to evacuate, do not hesitate. Move to a house built on high grounds.\n]n</li>
<li>Do not move outside the house immediately after the eye passes, as there will be wind gusts from the opposite direction.\n\n</li>
<li>Avoid rumours of any sort, and do not panic.\n\n</li>
<li>Do not drive immediately after a storm because the roads are left slippery due to heavy downpours.\n\n</li>
<li>Stay away from concrete walls and floors because thunder lightning can pass through the metal bars in them.\n\n</li>
</ul>

    </string>

    <string name="aftercyclone"><b>Safety measures to be taken after a cyclone :\n\n</b>
<ul>
<li>Eat fresh dry food and keep it away from pests and flies.\n\n</li>
<li>Boil water before drinking or cooking.\n\n</li>
<li>Keep your surroundings clean by using disinfectants.\n\n</li>
<li> Cover drains holes to prevent backflow of sewage.\n\n</li>
<li>Clear debris from your premises.\n\n</li>
<li>Stay in the shelter until you receive proper information regarding safety in moving outside.\n\n</li>
<li>Drive your car carefully after the cyclone passes.\n\n</li>
</ul>
        <p><b>Besides, there are some strict activities associated with safety measures after a cyclonic storm. They are as follows:\n\n</b></p>
<ul>
<li>Do not go near loose electric wires.\n\n</li>
<li>Avoid going to areas covered with floodwater.\n\n</li>
<li>Stay away from sewerage lines, gutters and drains.\n\n</li>
<li>Do not use tap water for drinking or cooking as the sewerage lines may be contaminated.\n\n</li>
</ul>

    </string>


    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>